* 
    
    Sign in to your account
    
* [
    
    Easy Reorder](https://nuts.com/account/easy-reorder)
* 
    
    0 items inYour Cart

Shop

Search

0

0 items in yourCart

Your Recent Searches

Search

FREE shipping on orders over $59!

FREE shipping on orders over $59!

* * *

\* For destinations within the contiguous U.S., orders totaling $59 or more (before tax) ship free and orders below $59 require payment for shipping. The price of shipping is available in Checkout. Multiple shipping addresses count separately. For other destinations (including international), shipping cost is calculated at checkout. Delivery date will be estimated at checkout. [See Full Details](https://nuts.com/shipping)

    * Featured

    * Gifts by Type

    * Gifts by Price

    * Gifts by Occasion

    * Gifts by Flavor

    [
    
    Build Your Own Box](https://nuts.com/custom/box/)
    
    [
    
    Shop Custom Trays](https://nuts.com/custom/trays/)

    * Featured

    * Shop By Specialty

    [
    
    Shop Organic Nuts](https://nuts.com/organic/nuts/)
    
    [
    
    Shop Our Best Sellers](https://nuts.com/nuts-seeds/best-sellers/)
    
* [###### Chocolates & Sweets Press arrowdown key to enter submenu](https://nuts.com/chocolatessweets/)
    
    * Featured

    [
    
    Shop S'mores](https://nuts.com/snacks/by-flavor/smores/)
    
    [
    
    Shop Candy By Color](https://nuts.com/colors/)

    * Snacks by Diet

    * Snacks by Region

    * Feel Good Snacks

    * Savory Snacks

    * Snacks by Activity

    [
    
    Custom Trail Mix](https://nuts.com/custom/mixes/)
    
    [
    
    Shop Our Trail Mixes](https://nuts.com/snacks/trail-mix/)

    * Featured

    * Fruity Snacks

    * Shop by Use

    [
    
    Shop No Sugar Added](https://nuts.com/driedfruit/no-sugar-added/)
    
    [
    
    Shop Chocolate Covered Fruit](https://nuts.com/driedfruit/chocolate-covered/)

    * Coffee by Roast

    * Shop by Type

    * Tea

    * Shop by Specialty

    [
    
    Shop Best Selling Coffees](https://nuts.com/coffeesteas/coffees)
    
    [
    
    Shop All Coffee & Tea](https://nuts.com/coffeesteas/coffees/)
    
* [###### Superfood Powders Press arrowdown key to enter submenu](https://nuts.com/cookingbaking/powders/)
    
    * Featured

    * New Products

    * Shop by Type

    * Shop by Use

    [
    
    Shop Organic Powders](https://nuts.com/cookingbaking/organic-powders/)
    
    [
    
    Shop Best Selling Powders](https://nuts.com/powders/best-sellers)

    * Shop by Diet

    * Pantry Essentials

    * Pantry Essentials

    * Cooking Staples

    [
    
    Shop Organic](https://nuts.com/cooking/organic/)
    
    [
    
    Stock Your Pantry](https://nuts.com/cms/pantry-staples)

    * Shop by Diet

    * Baking Ingredients

    * Nuts & Dried Fruits

    [
    
    Shop Nuts for Baking](https://nuts.com/chocolatessweets/toppings/nuts/chopped/)
    
    [
    
    Shop Herbs & Spices](https://nuts.com/baking/baking-spices/)

Main Content

Privacy Policy
==============

**Last Updated: February 15, 2024**

Thank you for visiting Nuts.com website located at www.nuts.com (the “Site”). The Site is an Internet property of Nuts.com, Inc. (“Nuts.com,” “we” or “our”). This Nuts.com Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) covers our treatment of personal information and other information that we collect when end-users (“User”, “you” or “your”): (a) access or use the Site; (b) access and/or download any of the: (i) text, audio, video, photographs, graphics, artwork, testimonials and/or other content featured on the Site (collectively, “Informational Content”); and/or (ii) links to third party websites, products and/or services (“Third-Party Links”, and together with the Informational Content, the “Content”); (c) access links to Nuts.com's social media pages/accounts (collectively, “Social Media Pages”) on third-party social media websites, such as Facebook®, Instagram®, LinkedIn®, Pinterest®, Twitter® and YouTube® (“Social Media Websites”); (d) purchase Nuts.com products featured on the Site (collectively, “Nuts.com Products”); (e) register to receive the Nuts.com e-mail newsletter (“Newsletter”); and/or (f) utilize the various contact forms and/or contact information made available on the Site as a means to contact directly, or request to be contacted by, Nuts.com (collectively, the “Contact Services,” and together with the Site, Content, Social Media Pages, Nuts.com Products and Newsletter, the “Site Offerings”). **Please note, if you are a resident of, or reside in, the United Kingdom or a European Union Member State, you are not permitted to use the Site and/or Site Offerings.**

Users with disabilities who wish to access this Privacy Policy in an alternative format can contact us by e-mailing us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); by calling us at: 1-800-558-6887 or by sending us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.

Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meanings set forth in the Nuts.com Website Terms and Conditions (“Terms and Conditions”). **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY IN THEIR ENTIRETY, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE OFFERINGS.**

Instagram® and Facebook® are registered trademarks of Facebook, Inc. LinkedIn® is a registered trademark of LinkedIn Corporation. Pinterest® is a registered trademark of Pinterest, Inc. Twitter® is a registered trademark of Twitter, Inc. YouTube® is a registered trademark of Google, Inc. Please be advised that Nuts.com is not in any way affiliated with Facebook, nor are the Site Offerings endorsed, administered or sponsored by any of the aforementioned entities.

State Specific Privacy Rights
-----------------------------

Residents of the States of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Delaware, Indiana, Iowa, Montana, New Jersey, Oregon, Tennessee, Texas, Utah and Virginia, businesses organized under the laws of the State of California, as well as California-based employees of, and Covered Users who submit job applicants to, Nuts.com (collectively, **“Covered Users”**), are afforded additional rights pursuant to applicable state law. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights as a Covered User.

1\. Your California Privacy Rights

Shine the Light. If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to learn how your “personal information” (as defined in the Shine the Light Law, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83) is shared with third-parties, what categories of personal information we have shared with third-parties in the preceding year, as well as the names and addresses of those third-parties, please e-mail us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); call us at: (800) 558-6887; or send us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.

Further, if you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third-party for marketing purposes, please e-mail us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); call us at: (800) 558-6887; or send us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016. Please be advised that where California State residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with applicable law.

Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“**CCPA**”) as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act "CPRA". In addition to the foregoing, if you are a resident of the State of California, certain other privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the CCPA and CPRA, including the right to opt-out of our sale of your personal information, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. In addition, you have the right to correct and/or delete personal information we have collected about you, the right to limit/opt-out of our use/sharing of your sensitive personal information, the right to know how long we retain your sensitive and non-sensitive personal information, the right to know what sensitive personal information about you we have collected, whether your sensitive personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of sensitive personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that sensitive personal information. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users" [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the CCPA as a California State resident.

Browser “Do Not Track” Signals. Most browsers contain a “do-not-track” setting. In general, when a “do-not-track” setting is active, the user’s browser notifies other websites that the user does not want her/his personal information and online behavior to be tracked and used, for example, for interest-based advertising. As required by California Online Privacy Protection Act (“**CalOPPA**”), we are required to inform you that, as is the case with most websites, we do not honor or alter our behavior when a Site user has activated the “do-not-track” setting on her/his browser; provided, however, that you may have certain rights with respect to the use of automated technologies to deliver targeted advertising to you, as well as to create profiles about you using your personal information.

2\. Your Colorado Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Colorado, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Colorado Privacy Act (“**CPA**”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information and the right to opt-out of the processing of your personal information for profiling/targeted advertising purposes, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. In addition, you have the right to opt-in to the processing of sensitive data and the right to opt-out of automated decision-making. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the CPA as a Colorado State resident.

3\. Your Connecticut Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Connecticut, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Connecticut Data Privacy Act (“**CDPA**”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information and the right to opt-out of the processing of your personal information for profiling/targeted advertising purposes, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. In addition, you have the right to opt-in to the processing of sensitive data and the right to opt-out of automated decision-making. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the CDPA as a Connecticut State resident.

4\. Your Delaware Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Delaware, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Delaware Personal Data Privacy Act (“DPDPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information and the right to opt-out of the processing of your personal information for profiling/targeted advertising purposes, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. In addition, you have the right to opt-in to the processing of sensitive data and the right to opt-out of automated decision-making. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the DPDPA as a Delaware State resident.

5\. Your Indiana Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Indiana, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Indiana Consumer Data Protection Act (“Indiana CDPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information and the right to opt-out of the processing of your personal information for profiling/targeted advertising purposes, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. In addition, you have the right to opt-in to the processing of sensitive data and the right to opt out of automated decision-making. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the Indiana CDPA as an Indiana State resident.

6\. Your Iowa Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Iowa, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Iowa Consumer Data Protection Act (“Iowa CDPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the Iowa CDPA as an Iowa State resident.

7\. Your Montana Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Montana, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Montana Consumer Data Privacy Act (“MCDPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information and the right to opt-out of the processing of your personal information for profiling/targeted advertising purposes, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. In addition, you have the right to opt-in to the processing of sensitive data and the right to opt-out of automated decision-making. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the MCDPA as a Montana State resident.

8\. Your New Jersey Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of New Jersey, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the New Jersey Data Privacy Act (“NJDPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information and the right to opt-out of the processing of your personal information for profiling/targeted advertising purposes, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. In addition, you have the right to opt-in to the processing of sensitive data and the right to opt-out of automated decision-making. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the NJDPA as a New Jersey State resident.

9\. Your Oregon Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Oregon, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Oregon Consumer Privacy Act (“OCPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information and the right to opt-out of the processing of your personal information for profiling/targeted advertising purposes, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. In addition, you have the right to opt-in to the processing of sensitive data and the right to opt-out of automated decision-making. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the OCPA as an Oregon State resident.

10\. Your Tennessee Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Tennessee, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Tennessee Information Protection Act (“TIPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information and the right to opt-out of the processing of your personal information for profiling/targeted advertising purposes, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. In addition, you have the right to opt-in to the processing of sensitive data and the right to opt-out of automated decision-making. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the TIPA as an Tennessee State resident.

11\. Your Texas Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Texas, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Texas Data Privacy and Security Act (“TDPSA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information and the right to opt-out of the processing of your personal information for profiling/targeted advertising purposes, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. In addition, you have the right to opt-in to the processing of sensitive data and the right to opt-out of automated decision-making. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the TDPSA as an Texas State resident.

12\. Your Nevada Privacy Rights

Nevada State residents have the right to submit opt-out requests to website operators instructing those website operators not to sell any “covered information” that the website operators have collected about Nevada State residents to any third party data broker(s). Covered information includes a consumer’s name, postal and email address, telephone number and Social Security Number, and includes the Information described [below](#personal-information-collected) in the “Personal Information Collected” section.

If you are a Nevada State resident and you wish to exercise your right to request that we to stop the sale of your Information to third party data brokers, please e-mail us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); call us at: (800) 558-6887; or send us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016. In your request, please specify that you want to exercise your rights to opt-out from the sale of covered information under the Nevada Privacy Law and specify the website that you visited and the email address you registered with. Please allow thirty (30) days for a response.

13\. Your Virginia Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Virginia, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (“VCDPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the VCDPA as a Virginia State resident.

14\. Your Utah Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of Utah, certain privacy-related rights may apply to you in accordance with the Utah Consumer Privacy Act (“UCPA”), including the right to opt-out of our sale/sharing of your personal information, as well as the right to know what personal information about you we have collected, whether your personal information was shared with third-parties in the preceding year and, if so, what categories of personal information were shared, as well as the categories of third parties with whom we shared that personal information. Please see our “Privacy Provisions for Covered Users” [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for a more complete description of your rights under the UCPA as a Utah State resident.

Appeals

If you are in a jurisdiction that recognizes your ability to appeal a decision we have made in connection with your attempt to assert a right under applicable US State Privacy Laws (such as Texas, Oregon, Montana, Colorado, Connecticut or Virginia), you may file an appeal of our decision refusing your request to exercise your rights under this Privacy Notice. Requests to change our policies or practices are not grounds for appeal. You may request an appeal of such decision by contacting us at [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com), please provide the state that you are writing from, accompanied with documentation you may have regarding the matter you are appealing. If your jurisdiction allows you to file a complaint with the state’s Attorney General’s Office regarding any concerns with the result of your appeal request, you may do so by using the following links: [Virginia](https://www.oag.state.va.us/consumer-protection/index.php/file-a-complaint), [Colorado](https://coag.gov/file-complaint/), [Connecticut](https://portal.ct.gov/AG/Common/Complaint-Form-Landing-page), and [Texas](https://oag.my.salesforce-sites.com/CPDOnlineForm).

General Privacy Provisions
--------------------------

Privacy Policy Quick Links
--------------------------

Below are links to key sections of our Privacy Policy:

Personal Information Collected
------------------------------

Please see our Privacy Provisions for Covered Users [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for additional details regarding the categories of personal information collected.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “personal information” shall mean individually identifiable information from or about an individual. We collect personal information when you access certain of the Site Offerings and complete the required information request form(s) and/or otherwise provide such information to us. The information that you must supply on the form(s) may include, without limitation: (a) your name; (b) your mailing/billing address (where purchasing Nuts.com Products); (c) your e-mail address; (d) your telephone number; (e) your credit card information (where purchasing Nuts.com Products); and/or (f) any other information requested by us on the Form.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, item (e) in the preceding paragraph will be considered “Sensitive Information.”

Use and Sharing of Personal Information
---------------------------------------

Please see our Privacy Provisions for Covered Users below [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for details regarding our use and sharing of personal information.

Nuts.com will never share, sell, rent, exchange or barter your personal information to or with any third-party for financial gain or marketing purposes. By making your personal information available to Nuts.com, you grant Nuts.com the right, subject to applicable law, to use that personal information (other than Sensitive Information) to contact you by telephone and email regarding your use of the Site Offerings (including in connection with any purchase of Nuts.com Products). If you wish to stop receiving future communications from us, please follow the instructions at the end of each such marketing message or see the "Opt-Out/Unsubscribe" section below. We may also use your personal information to send you promotional messages regarding various Nuts.com products and/or services, as well as third-party products and/or services that we think may be of interest to you. If you wish to stop receiving future communications from us, please follow the instructions at the end of each such marketing message or use any of the other options available in the “Opt-Out/Unsubscribe” section below.

Where you submit personal information, we use the personal information that you make available to facilitate the delivery of the applicable Site Offerings to you, including to respond to any inquiries made by you. You also agree that we may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your continued use of the Site Offerings, and to keep you informed of our other products and services.

We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card and other payment transactions, sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from User lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. The agents performing these limited functions on our behalf shall have access to our Users' personal information (including Sensitive Information, where applicable) as needed to perform these functions for us, but we do not permit them to use User personal information for other purposes.

We will also use your personal information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request, to customize your experience with the Site Offerings and/or to contact you for market research purposes. We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our service offerings including, without limitation, the Site Offerings. We may also combine the information we have gathered about you with information from other sources.

By submitting your personal information by and through the Site Offerings, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR §310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the “Rule”) and applicable state do-not-call regulations. As such, notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, and/or on applicable state do-not-call lists, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the Rule and applicable state do-not-call regulations.

Where you provide “prior express consent” within the meaning of the Telephone Consumer Protection Act (47 USC § 227), and its implementing regulations adopted by the Federal Communications Commission (47 CFR § 64.1200), as amended from time-to-time (“TCPA”), you consent to receive, from Nuts.com, telephone calls, including artificial voice calls, pre-recorded messages and/or calls (including text alerts via SMS text messages delivered via automated technology, to the telephone number(s) that you provided. Please note that you are not required to provide this consent in order to obtain access to the Site Offerings, and your consent simply allows Nuts.com to contact you via these means. **Please be advised that by agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you are obligated to immediately inform us if and when the telephone number that you have previously provided to us changes. Without limiting the foregoing, if you: (a) have your telephone number reassigned to another person or entity; (b) give up your telephone number so that it is no longer used by you; (c) port your telephone number to a landline or vice versa; or (d) otherwise stop using that telephone number for any reason (collectively “Phone Number Change”), you agree that you shall promptly notify Nuts.com of the Phone Number Change via e-mail at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com), or by using one of the methods set forth in the “Contact Us” section below.**

We reserve the right to release current or past personal information (including Sensitive Information): (i) in the event that we believe that the Site Offerings are being or have been used in violation of the Terms and Conditions or to commit unlawful acts; (ii) if the information is subpoenaed; provided, however, that, where permitted by applicable law, we shall provide you with e-mail notice, and opportunity to challenge the subpoena, prior to disclosure of any personal information pursuant to a subpoena; (iii) if we are sold, merge with a third-party or are acquired by a third-party (collectively, “**M&A Transactions**”) (including where we share your personal information, including Sensitive Information, in connection with the due diligence process associated with a potential M&A Transaction); or (iv) if we are the subject of bankruptcy proceedings; provided, however, that if Nuts.com is involved in a bankruptcy proceeding or M&A Transaction, you will be notified via e-mail and/or a prominent notice on the Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices that you may have regarding your personal information.

You hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or communication to any third-party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be required by applicable law, including sharing your e-mail address with third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, and other e-mail marketing laws. Users should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, might have the authority under certain circumstances to permit personal information to be shared or transferred to third-parties without permission.

Credit and/or Debit Card Transactions
-------------------------------------

Nuts.com utilizes third-party service providers to provide credit and debit card payment processing services. If you choose to purchase Nuts.com Products, the credit or debit card information provided will be shared with our contracted third-party payment processing service provider(s). Nuts.com requires that its third-party payment processing service provider(s) has/have in place privacy policies and practices consistent with this Privacy Policy; provided, however, that we cannot guarantee the privacy practices of our third-party payment processing service provider(s).

Non-Personal Information Collection and Use
-------------------------------------------

Please see our Privacy Provisions for Covered Users [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for more details regarding the categories and types of non-personal information collected.

### Computer IP Addresses/Browser Type

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you and your desktop computer when you visit many of the pages of the Site. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation, the type of browser that you use (e.g., Safari, Chrome, Internet Explorer), your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or iOS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Verizon, AT&T). We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site Offerings and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze usage of the Site Offerings.

### Cookies

When a User visits the Site, we send one (1) or more cookies and/or gif files (collectively, "**Cookies**") to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the applicable User's computer and/or mobile device, as applicable. A Cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience on the Site, as applicable. To find out more about Cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com. We use Cookies to improve the quality of the Site Offerings, including for storing User preferences and tracking Site usage (such as pages opened and length of stay at the Site, as applicable).

Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept Cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. To disable and reject certain Cookies, follow the instructions associated with your Internet browser. Even in the case where a User rejects a Cookie, he or she may still use the Site Offerings; provided, however, that certain functions of the Site Offerings may be impaired or rendered inoperable if the use of Cookies is disabled. We reserve the right to retain Cookie data indefinitely.

### Behavioral Tracking

Nuts.com and its third-party partners use Cookies, pixels and other tracking technology (collectively, "**Tracking Technology**") to analyze trends, administer the Site, track Users' movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our User base as a whole. In addition, we partner with third-parties such as Facebook ® to use Tracking Technology in connection with the serving of our advertising to you on other websites when you exit the Site. Our third-party partners may use Tracking Technology to gather information about your activities on the Site and other websites in order to provide you with certain Nuts.com advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.

Users may be able to disable some, but not all, of this tracking activity by utilizing the "Do Not Track" setting or similar options within most major Internet browsers. Further, Users may be able to opt-out of this form of tracking utilizing the options made available by the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads) or [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/). Please note that opting out of this tracking activity does not opt you out of being served advertising. Even where you opt out of this tracking activity, you will continue to receive generic ads.

### Live Chat/Chat Bots

Nuts.com utilizes third-party service providers to provide live chat and automated chat services (collectively, “Chat”) to Users on the Site. These third party Chat service providers, including Kustomer, LLC, may collect and store the content of these Chat conversations, and will share same with Nuts.com; provided, however, that these third-party Chat service providers are not permitted to utilize User personal information collected via Chat conversations for any purpose other than: (a) to provide the Chat services on the Site; and (b) to assist Nuts.com with the customer service functionality associated with the Chat services. Please see our Privacy Provisions for Covered Users [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for details regarding our use and sharing of personal information.

### Cross Device Tracking

Nuts.com tracks Users' use of the Site Offerings across various devices, including your personal computer and mobile device, in order to optimize and personalize your Site Offerings experience. Nuts.com may collect certain of your personal information across various devices. Please be advised that where you opt-out of having your use of the Site Offerings tracked across devices, you may need to upload certain information multiple times and/or input your log-in information multiple times.

### Aggregate Data

Nuts.com reserves the right to transfer and/or sell aggregate or group data about Users of the Site Offerings for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage and other characteristics of Users as a group, without disclosing personally identifiable information.

Social Media Websites
---------------------

If you engage in any interaction with Nuts.com, other Users or any third-party on any Social Media Pages, you should be aware that: (a) the personal information that you submit by and through such Social Media Pages can be read, collected and/or used by other Users of these websites/services (depending on your privacy settings associated with your accounts with the applicable Social Media Websites), and could be used to send you unsolicited messages or otherwise to contact you without your consent or desire; and (b) where Nuts.com responds to any interaction on such Social Media Pages, your account name/handle may be viewable by any and all members/Users of Nuts.com's social media accounts. We are not responsible for the personal information that you choose to submit on any Social Media Websites.

Your interactions with the Social Media Pages are governed by the privacy policies of the applicable Social Media Websites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and settings of the Social Media Pages with which you interact to help you understand those Social Media Websites' respective privacy practices. If you have questions about the security and privacy settings of any Social Media Pages that you use, please refer to the applicable Social Media Website's privacy notices or policies.

Third-Party Websites
--------------------

This Site may contain links to third-party owned and/or operated websites including, without limitation, Social Media Websites, as well as the websites of other third parties. Nuts.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be able to make a purchase through one of these third-party websites. In these instances, you may be required to provide certain information, such as a credit card number, to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and Nuts.com has no responsibility or liability relating to them.

### Rakuten Advertising Statement

Rakuten Advertising may collect personal information when you interact with our digital property, including IP addresses, digital identifiers, information about your web browsing and app usage and how you interact with our properties and ads for a variety of purposes, such as personalization of offers or advertisements, analytics about how you engage with websites or ads and other commercial purposes. For more information about the collection, use and sale of your personal data and your rights, please use the below links.

Privacy policy : [https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-policy](https://go.rakutenadvertising.com/hubfs/Services-Privacy-Policy-English.pdf)  
Your rights : [Services Privacy Rights Request Form | Rakuten Advertising](https://rakutenadvertising.com/legal-notices/services-privacy-rights-request-form)

Security of Your Personal Information
-------------------------------------

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our Users' personal information. When Users make personal information available to us, their personal information is protected both online and offline (to the extent that we maintain any personal information offline). Where our registration/application process prompts Users to enter Sensitive Information (such as credit card information), and when we store and transmit such Sensitive Information, that information is encrypted with advanced TLS (Transport Layer Security).

Access to your personal information is strictly limited, and we take reasonable security measures to ensure that your personal information is not accessible to the public. All of our Users' personal information is restricted in our offices, as well as the offices of our third-party service providers. Only employees or third-party agents who need User personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to User personal information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all User personal information. Employees not adhering to our firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. The servers that we store User personal information on are kept in a secure physical environment. We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control.

Please be advised, however, that while we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your data, no storage facility, technology, software, security protocols or data transmission over the Internet or via wireless networks can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Computer hackers that circumvent our security measures may gain access to certain portions of your personal information, and technological bugs, errors and glitches may cause inadvertent disclosures of your personal information; provided, however, that any attempt to breach the security of the network, our servers, databases or other hardware or software may constitute a crime punishable by law. For the reasons mentioned above, we cannot warrant that your personal information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through the Site, other Site Offerings or otherwise via the Internet or wireless networks, is done at your own risk.

In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

Children's Privacy
------------------

Please see our Privacy Provisions for Covered Users [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for more details regarding the personal information of minors.

Visitors under eighteen (18) years of age are not permitted to use and/or submit their personal information at the Site. Nuts.com does not knowingly solicit or collect information from visitors under eighteen (18) years of age.

SMS Communications Policy
-------------------------

When you opt-in to the service, we will send you an SMS message to confirm your signup.

You can cancel this service at any time. Just text "STOP" to 466-887. After you send the message "STOP" to us, we will send you a reply message to confirm that you have been unsubscribed. After this, you will no longer receive messages from us. If you want to join again, just sign up as you did the first time, and we will start sending messages to you again. If at any time you forget what keywords are supported, just text "HELP" to 466-887. After you send the message "HELP" to us, we will respond with instructions on how to use our service as well as how to unsubscribe.

We are able to deliver messages to the following mobile phone carriers

**Major Carriers:** AT&T, Verizon Wireless, Sprint, T-Mobile  
**Minor Carriers:** U.S. Cellular, Boost Mobile, MetroPCS, Virgin Mobile, Alaska Communications Systems (ACS), Appalachian Wireless (EKN), Bluegrass Cellular, Cellular One of East Central, IL (ECIT), Cellular One of Northeast Pennsylvania, Cricket, Coral Wireless (Mobi PCS), COX, Cross, Element Mobile (Flat Wireless), Epic Touch (Elkhart Telephone), GCI, Golden State, Hawkeye (Chat Mobility), Hawkeye (NW Missouri), Illinois Valley Cellular, Inland Cellular, iWireless (Iowa Wireless), Keystone Wireless (Immix Wireless/PC Man), Mosaic (Consolidated or CTC Telecom), Nex-Tech Wireless, NTelos, Panhandle Communications, Pioneer, Plateau (Texas RSA 3 Ltd), Revol, RINA, Simmetry (TMP Corporation), Thumb Cellular, Union Wireless, United Wireless, Viaero Wireless, and West Central (WCC or 5 Star Wireless).

As always, Message and Data Rates May Apply for any messages sent to you from us and to us from you. If you have any questions about your text plan or data plan, it is best to contact your wireless provider. For all questions about the services provided by this short code, you can send an email to [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com).

Opt-Out/Unsubscribe
-------------------

Please see our Privacy Provisions for Covered Users [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for instructions on how Covered Users can opt-out of the sale of their personal information to third parties.

To opt-out of receiving e-mail and other forms of communication from us, you can: (a) follow the instructions included in the applicable e-mail message or other communication; (b) update your e-mail communication preferences in your Account Settings [here](https://nuts.com/account); or (c) e-mail us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com).

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to your request for Site Offerings, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you. To opt-out of receiving Site Offerings-related and/or inquiry response-related messages from Nuts.com, you must cease requesting and/or utilizing the Site Offerings and/or cease submitting inquiries to Nuts.com, as applicable.

Deleting, Modifying and Updating Your Information
-------------------------------------------------

Please see our Privacy Provisions for Covered Users [below](#privacy-provisions-for-covered-users) for instructions on how Covered Users can access and/or delete personal information that we have collected.

At your request, we will: (a) inform you of what personal information we have on file for you; (b) amend the personal information that we have on file for you; and/or (c) remove personal information that you have provided to us, or that we have otherwise collected. You may do so by e-mailing us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com). We ask individual Users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and, to the extent permitted by applicable law, we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).

Please be advised that deleting your personal information may terminate your access to certain of the Site Offerings. If you wish to continue using the full complement of Site Offerings, you may not be able to delete all of the personal information that we have on file for you.

Please be further advised that, after you delete your personal information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.

Transfer of Personal Information Internationally
------------------------------------------------

If you are visiting the Site from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, your communications with us may result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting the Site and/or otherwise communicating electronically with us, you consent to such transfers. Even if your jurisdiction does not have the same privacy laws as the jurisdiction where our servers are located, we will treat your information as subject to the protections described in this Privacy Policy.

Changes to this Privacy Policy
------------------------------

Nuts.com reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice on the Site that we are changing our Privacy Policy. If the manner in which we use personal information changes, Nuts.com will notify Users by: (a) sending the modified policy to our Users via e-mail; and/or (b) by any other reasonable means acceptable under applicable state and federal law. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner and we will only use your information in this different manner where you opt-in to such use.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices in general, you may e-mail us as at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); call us at: (800) 558-6887; or send us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.

Privacy Provisions for Covered Users
====================================

These Privacy Provisions for Covered Users (“Privacy Provisions”) supplement, and do not limit in any way, the Privacy Policy set forth above. These Privacy Provisions apply solely to the Covered Users, who are residents of the States of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Virginia and Utah, as well as businesses organized under the laws of the State of California. We adopt these Provisions in compliance with the CCPA, CPRA, CPA, CDPA, VCDPA and UCPA (collectively, “**Applicable State Laws**”). Any terms defined in Applicable State Laws have the same meaning when used in these Privacy Provisions. Covered Users with disabilities who wish to access these Privacy Provisions in an alternative format can contact us by emailing us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); calling us at: (800) 558-6887; or sending us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.

Categories of Information We Collect
------------------------------------

We collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular Covered User or device (“personal information”). In particular, we have collected the following categories of personal information from Covered Users within the last twelve (12) months:

| Category | Examples | Collected |
| --- | --- | --- |
| A. Identifiers. | A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, telephone number, or other similar identifiers. | YES |
| B. Personal information categories listed in Applicable State Laws. | A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, postal address, telephone number, passport number, driver's license or State identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories. | YES |
| C. Protected classification characteristics under Applicable State Laws or federal law. | Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or military status, genetic information (including familial genetic information). | NO  |
| D. Commercial information. | Records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. | YES |
| E. Biometric information. | Genetic, physiological, behavioral, and biological characteristics, or activity patterns used to extract a template or other identifier or identifying information, such as, fingerprints, faceprints, and voiceprints, iris or retina scans, keystroke, gait, or other physical patterns, and sleep, health, or exercise data. | NO  |
| F. Internet or other similar network activity. | Browsing history, search history, information on a Covered User's interaction with a website, application or advertisement. | YES |
| G. Geolocation data. | Physical location or movements. | NO  |
| H. Sensory data. | Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information. | NO  |
| I. Professional or employment-related information. | Current or past job history or performance evaluations. | YES |
| J. Non-public education information (per the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. Section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)). | Education records directly related to a student maintained by an educational institution or party acting on its behalf, such as grades, transcripts, class lists, student schedules, student identification codes, student financial information, or student disciplinary records. | NO  |
| K. Inferences drawn from other personal information. | Profile reflecting a person's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes. | NO  |
| L. Sensitive Personal Information. | A Social Security number, driver’s license number, state identification card number, or passport number. Account log-in information, financial account, or debit or credit card number used in combination with any required security code, access code, password, or log-in credentials necessary to access an account. Precise geolocation, racial or ethnic origin, religious or philosophical beliefs, or union membership. The contents of a consumer’s U.S. mail, electronic mail, or text messages unless the business is the intended recipient, and a consumer’s genetic data. | YES |

Personal information does not include:

* Publicly available information from government records.
* De-identified or aggregated Covered User information.
* Information excluded from the scope of Applicable State Laws, such as:
    * health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) and the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA) or clinical trial data; and
    * personal information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FRCA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) or California Financial Information Privacy Act (FIPA), and the Driver's Privacy Protection Act of 1994.

We obtain the categories of personal information listed above (including (a) name; (b) mailing/billing address; (c) e-mail address; (d) telephone number; and (e) credit card information) from the following categories of sources:

* Directly from our Covered Users. For example, from online registration forms that our Covered Users submit to us in connection with the products and/or services that we offer by and through the Site and/or provided through the course of employment and/or through job application. (Categories A, B, D, I and L)
* Indirectly from our Covered Users. For example, through information we collect from our Covered Users in the course of providing our products and/or services to them. (Categories A, B, D, F and L)
* Directly and indirectly from activity on the Site. This includes the type of browser that the Covered User uses (e.g., Safari, Chrome, Internet Explorer), Covered User IP address, the type of operating system used by the Covered User (e.g., Windows or iOS) and the domain name of the Covered User's Internet Service Provider. In addition, we obtain certain Site usage details and analytics as same are collected automatically by us and our third party partners such as Facebook®, Rakuten Advertising, and our third party Chat service providers, including Kustomer LLC. (Category F)
* When our Covered Users interact with us on our social media accounts, including commenting on and/or liking our posts. (Categories A, B, D and F)
* From third-parties that interact with us in connection with the products and/or services that we offer to our Covered Users. For example, third party entities that assist us in sending direct and electronic mail, targeting advertisements, removing duplicate information from Covered User lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. (Categories A, B, D, F and L)

### Retention of Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Information

We retain all categories of your personal information and Sensitive Information that we collect for the maximum period permitted by applicable law. We may also use certain criteria to determine whether and when to delete certain categories of collected personal and sensitive personal information including:

* Date of collection.
* Frequency of consumer interaction with us.
* Last interaction the consumer had with us.
* Whether the purpose of collection has been completed.

### Use of Personal Information

We may use or disclose the personal information that we collect (including (a) name; (b) mailing/billing address; (c) e-mail address; (d) telephone number; and (e) credit card information) for one or more of the following business purposes:

* To fulfill or meet the reason for which the information is provided. For example, if you provide us with personal information in connection with your request for products and/or services, we will use that information to process your request. (Categories A, B, D, F and L)
* To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us. (Categories A, B, D, F and L)
* To create, maintain, customize and secure your account with us. (Categories A, B, D, F and L)
* To provide you with e-mail, direct mail and telemarketing messages concerning certain Nuts.com products and/or services, as well as third-party products and/or services, that we believe may be of interest to you. (Categories A, B, D and F)
* To deliver relevant Site content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you. (Categories A, B, D and F)
* To carry out operations associated with, or your employment and/or job application submitted to, us. (Categories A, B, D, I and L)
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including the Site's Terms and Conditions. (Categories A, B, D, F, I and L)
* To improve the Site and better present its contents to you. (Categories A, B, D, F and L)
* For customer service purposes and to respond to inquiries from you. (Categories A, B, D, F and L)
* To communicate with you during and following your Chat conversations with us and our third party Chat service providers. (Categories A, B, D, F and L)
* For testing, research, analysis and product development. (Categories A, B, D, F and L)
* As necessary or appropriate to protect our rights, property or safety, and that of our customers or others. (Categories A, B, D, F, I and L)
* To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations. (Categories A, B, D, F, I and L)
* As described to you when collecting your personal information or as otherwise set forth in Applicable State Law. (Categories A, B, D, F, I and L)
* To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us is among the assets transferred. (Categories A, B, D, F, I and L)

We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information we collected for materially different, unrelated or incompatible purposes without providing you with notice.

### Sharing Personal Information

Subject to your right to opt-out of such sharing/sale, we may share your personal information (including (a) name; (b) mailing/billing address; (c) e-mail address; (d) telephone number; and (e) credit card information) for the business purposes set forth above. 

When we disclose personal information to a third party service provider or other entity, we enter into a contractual relationship that describes the purpose for which such third party may use the personal information and requires that third party to both keep the personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose other than the performance of its services under the applicable contract. Please note, we do not collect information from Covered Users that we actually know are less than eighteen (18) years of age and we do not share or sell the personal information of Covered Users that we actually know are less than eighteen (18) years of age. Without limiting the foregoing, we have not shared or sold the personal information of Covered Users that we actually know are less than sixteen (16) years of age in the preceding twelve (12) months.

In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have disclosed the following categories of personal information (including (a) name; (b) mailing/billing address; (c) e-mail address; (d) telephone number; and (e) credit card information) for a business purpose:

Category A Identifiers.  
Category B Personal information categories listed in Applicable State Laws.  
Category D Commercial information.  
Category F Internet or other similar network activity.  
Category I Professional or employment-related information (but only for facilitating the relationship with Covered User job applicants and employees).  
Category L Sensitive Information (solely for purposes of processing purchases of Nuts.com Products).  

We disclose your personal information (including (a) name; (b) mailing/billing address; (c) e-mail address; (d) telephone number; and (e) credit card information) for a business purpose to the following categories of third parties:

* Our affiliates. (Categories A, B, D and F)
* Service providers. (Categories A, B, D, F, I and L)
* Third parties who provide the products and/or services featured on the Site. (Categories A, B, D and F)
* Third parties to whom you authorize us to disclose your personal information in connection with the products and/or services that we provide to you. (Categories A, B, D, F, I and L)

In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have not sold any personal information to third parties, or shared your personal information with third parties for marketing purposes.

### Your Rights and Choices

Applicable State Laws provides Covered Users (Covered Users) with specific rights regarding their personal information. This section describes your rights under Applicable State Laws and explains how to exercise those rights.

### Opt-Out from the Sale of Your Personal Information

While we have not sold personal information to third parties in the preceding twelve (12) months, you have the right to opt-out of our sale of your personal information to third parties. To exercise your right to opt-out of our sale of your personal information to third parties, please submit a verifiable Covered User request to us by either:

* Clicking here: [https://nuts.com/ccpa-opt-out](https://nuts.com/ccpa-opt-out);
* Calling us at: 1-800-558-6887;
* Emailing us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); or
* Sending us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.

We endeavor to act on all opt-out requests as soon as practicable, but in all cases within fifteen (15) business days of the receipt of your request.

### Opt-Out from the Sharing of Your Personal Information

You have the right to opt-out of our sharing your personal information with third parties. To exercise your right to opt-out of our sharing your personal information with third parties, please submit a verifiable Covered User request to us by either:

* Clicking here: [https://nuts.com/ccpa-opt-out](https://nuts.com/ccpa-opt-out);
* Calling us at: 1-800-558-6887;
* Emailing us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); or
* Sending us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.

We endeavor to act on all opt-out requests as soon as practicable, but in all cases within fifteen (15) business days of the receipt of your request. Subject to the aforementioned fifteen (15) business day period, where we receive and confirm your verifiable opt-out request, we will cease sharing your Personal Information with third parties.

### Opt-Out from the User and/or Sharing of Your Sensitive Personal Information

You have the right to limit our use of your sensitive personal information, including any sensitive information from Category B (Personal information categories established by Applicable State Laws), Category D (Commercial information), Category I (Professional or employment-related information) and/or Category L (Sensitive Personal Information), to those uses which: (i) are necessary to perform the services or provide the goods requested by you; (ii) help us to ensure security and integrity of your personal information to the extent the use of your sensitive personal information is reasonably necessary and proportionate for these purposes; (iii) are short-term, transient uses including, but not limited to, non-personalized advertising shown as part of your then-current interaction with the Site, provided that your personal information is not disclosed to another third party and is not used to build a profile about you or otherwise alter your experience outside the then-current interaction with the Site; (iv) involve performing services on behalf of Nuts.com, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing analytic services, providing storage, or providing similar services on behalf of Nuts.com; and (v) include activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned by, manufactured by, manufactured for, or controlled by, Nuts.com, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned by, manufactured by, manufactured for, or controlled by, Nuts.com.

You also have the right opt-out of our sharing your sensitive personal information with third parties, including any sensitive information from Category B (Personal information categories established by Applicable State Laws), Category D (Commercial information), Category I (Professional or employment-related information) and/or Category L (Sensitive Personal Information).

To exercise your right to limit our use of your sensitive personal information and/or opt-out of our sharing your sensitive personal information with third parties, please submit a verifiable Covered User request to us by either:

* Clicking here: [https://nuts.com/ccpa-opt-out](https://nuts.com/ccpa-opt-out);
* Calling us at: 1-800-558-6887;
* Emailing us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); or
* Sending us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.

We endeavor to act on all such requests as soon as practicable, but in all cases within fifteen (15) business days of the receipt of your request. Subject to the aforementioned fifteen (15) business day period, where we receive and confirm your verifiable opt-out request, we will cease using your Sensitive Personal Information/sharing your Sensitive Personal Information with third parties (and direct our service providers and contractors to do the same).

### Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights

You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past twelve (12) months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable Covered User access/portability request, we will disclose to you:

* The categories of personal information we collected about you.
* The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.
* Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.
* The categories of third parties with whom we have shared that personal information.
* The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you (also called a data portability request).
* If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, two separate lists disclosing:
    * sales, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient purchased; and
    * disclosures for a business purpose, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained.

### Deletion Request Rights

You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Subject to the time period allotted to comply with such requests, where we receive and confirm your verifiable Covered User deletion request, we will delete (and direct our service providers, contractors and third parties to whom we sold/shared your personal information, to delete) your personal information from our (their) records, unless an exception applies; provided, however, that in some cases, strictly for regulatory compliance purposes and to better evidence/honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests (and for no other purposes), we may retain certain items of your personal information on a de-identified and aggregated basis in such a manner that the data no longer identifies you.

We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service providers, contractors and/or third parties to whom we sold/shared your personal information, to:

1. Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform our obligations in connection with our contract/relationship with you.
2. Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.
3. Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
4. Exercise free speech rights, ensure the right of another Covered User to exercise her/his free speech rights or exercise another right provided for by law.
5. Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 seq.).
6. Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information's deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research's achievement, but only if you previously provided informed consent.
7. Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with Covered User expectations based on your relationship with us.
8. Comply with a legal obligation.
9. Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.

### Right to Request Correction of Inaccurate Personal or Sensitive Personal Information

You have the right to request correction of inaccurate personal and/or sensitive personal information that we collect. Upon receiving a verifiable consumer request for correction, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to correct information identified as inaccurate. Where we correct inaccurate personal and/or sensitive personal information, we shall instruct all service providers and/or contractors that maintain such personal and/or sensitive personal information in the course of providing services to us to make the necessary corrections in their respective systems.

### Exercising Access, Data Portability, Right to Correct and Deletion Rights

To exercise your access, data portability, right to correct and/or deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable Covered User request to us by either:

* Clicking here: [https://nuts.com/ccpa-privacy-rights-request](https://nuts.com/ccpa-privacy-rights-request);
* Calling us at: 1-800-558-6887;
* Emailing us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); or
* Sending us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.

The verifiable Covered User access, data portability, right to correct and/or deletion rights request must:

* Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify that you are: (1) the person about whom we collected personal information; or (2) an authorized representative.
* Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm that the personal information relates to you.  Making a verifiable Covered User access, data portability, right to correct and/or deletion rights request does not require that you create an account with us.  We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable Covered User request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.

Response Timing and Format
--------------------------

We endeavor to respond to all verifiable Covered User access, data portability, right to correct and/or deletion rights requests within forty-five (45) days of the receipt thereof.  If we require more time (up to ninety (90) days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.  We will deliver our written response by mail or electronically, at your option.  Any disclosures that we provide will only cover the twelve (12) month period preceding the receipt of your verifiable request.  The response that we provide will also explain the reasons that we cannot comply with a request, if applicable.  For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your personal information that is readily useable and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.

We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable Covered User request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded.  If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.

Right to Opt-Out of Profiling
-----------------------------

You have the right to opt-out from any Profiling that may be conducted by Nuts.com. For purposes of these Provisions, "Profiling" means any form of automated processing performed on your personal data to evaluate, analyze or predict personal aspects related to you or your economic situation, health, personal preferences, interests, reliability, behavior, location or movements. You have the right to opt-out of our Profiling you. To exercise your right to opt-out of our Profiling you, please submit a verifiable Covered User request to us by either:

* Clicking here: [https://nuts.com/ccpa-privacy-rights-request](https://nuts.com/ccpa-privacy-rights-request);
* Calling us at: 1-800-558-6887;
* Emailing us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); or
* Sending us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.

We endeavor to act on all Profiling opt-out requests as soon as practicable, but in all cases within forty-five (45) days of the receipt of your request.

Right to Opt-Out of Targeted Advertising
----------------------------------------

You have the right to opt-out from Targeted Advertising conducted by Nuts.com. For purposes of these Provisions, "Targeted Advertising” means displaying advertisements to you where the advertisements are selected based on personal data obtained from your activities over time and across nonaffiliated websites or online applications to predict your preferences or interests. You have the right to opt-out from Targeted Advertising. To exercise your right to opt-out of our Targeted Advertising, please submit a verifiable Covered User request to us by either:

* Clicking here: [https://nuts.com/ccpa-privacy-rights-request](https://nuts.com/ccpa-privacy-rights-request);
* Calling us at: 1-800-558-6887;
* Emailing us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); or
* Sending us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.

We endeavor to act on all Targeted Advertising opt-out requests as soon as practicable, but in all cases within forty-five (45) days of the receipt of your request.

Authorized Agents
-----------------

Covered Users may permit an Authorized Agent to exercise any rights granted under Applicable State Laws as set forth above. In order to utilize an Authorized Agent, you must provide the Authorized Agent with written permission from you to act on your behalf for these purposes. When you use an Authorized Agent to submit a request to delete, request to correct or a request to know, we may require the Authorized Agent to provide proof that you gave the agent signed permission to submit the subject request. We may also require you to do either of the following: (a) verify your own identity directly with us; or (b) directly confirm with us that you provided the Authorized Agent permission to submit the request.

For California residents, only you or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable Covered User request related to your personal information.

Non-Discrimination
------------------

We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights under Applicable State Laws. Unless permitted by Applicable State Laws, we will not:

* Deny you goods or services;
* Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties;
* Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services; and/or
* Retaliate against any employee, job applicant or independent contractor;
* Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

Changes to these Privacy Provisions
-----------------------------------

We reserve the right to amend these Privacy Provisions in our discretion and at any time. When we make changes to these Privacy Provisions, we will notify you by email or through a notice on the Site's homepage.

This fulfills the [Transparency in Coverage](https://alliedbenefit.sapphiremrfhub.com/) requirement.

Contact Information
-------------------

If you have any questions or comments about these Privacy Provisions, our Privacy Policy, the ways in which we collect and use your personal information, your choices and rights regarding such use, or wish to exercise your rights under Applicable State Laws, please do not hesitate to contact us by either:

* Clicking here: [https://nuts.com/contact](https://nuts.com/contact);
* Calling us at: 1-800-558-6887;
* Emailing us at: [care@nuts.com](mailto:care@nuts.com); or
* Sending us U.S. Mail to: Nuts.com, 125 Moen St., Cranford, NJ 07016.

* [](https://nuts.com/subscribe)**Sign up for our newsletter** Receive limited, email-only offers!
    
* **We love to socialize** Come join us on social media!

* * *

Order securely online or call us:

[800-558-6887](tel:+1-800-558-6887) or [908-523-0333](tel:+1-908-523-0333)

Operating Hours (ET):

Su 8am-4:30pm  
M-Th 8am-8pm  
F-Sa 8am-6:30pm

**100%** Committed to  
Our Customers
-------------------------------------

At Nuts.com, customer satisfaction is our top priority. If you experience a problem with our products, customer service, or shipping, please let us know.

**We’ll do whatever it takes to make it right. It’s a family tradition.**

© Copyright 1999-2024 Nuts.com
